list_of_questions =[
{
"question": "Height of the Burj Khalifa in meters",
"answer": 828
},
{
"question": "Height of Merdeka 118 in meters",
"answer": 679
},
{
"question": "Height of Shanghai Tower in meters",
"answer": 632
},
{
"question": "Height of Makkah Royal Clock Tower in meters",
"answer": 601
},
{
"question": "Height of Ping An Finance Center in meters",
"answer": 599
},
{
"question": "Maximum weight of a blue whale in tonnes",
"answer": 190
},
{
"question": "Maximum weight of an African bush elephant in tonnes",
"answer": 10
},
{
"question": "Maximum weight of a hippopotamus in tonnes",
"answer": 4
},
{
"question": "Top speed of a cheetah in km/h",
"answer": 120
},
{
"question": "Top speed of a pronghorn antelope in km/h",
"answer": 98
},
{
"question": "Top speed of a lion in km/h",
"answer": 80
},
{
"question": "Height of Mount Everest in meters",
"answer": 8848
},
{
"question": "Height of the Eiffel Tower in meters",
"answer": 324
},
{
"question": "Length of the Great Wall of China in km (total)",
"answer": 21196
},
{
"question": "Number of bones in an adult human body",
"answer": 206
},
{
"question": "Height difference: Eiffel Tower taller than Washington Monument in feet",
"answer": 300
},
{
"question": "Tallest unicycle ever mastered in feet",
"answer": 46
},
{
"question": "Number of M&Ms in a one-pound bag",
"answer": 425
},
{
"question": "Lifespan of a queen ant in years",
"answer": 7
},
{
"question": "Annual migration distance of a box turtle in miles",
"answer": 100
},
{
"question": "Number of vertebrae in giraffe neck",
"answer": 7
},
{
"question": "Average cruising altitude of commercial airplane in feet",
"answer": 36000
},
{
"question": "Length of the Amazon River in km",
"answer": 6992
},
{
"question": "Height of Statue of Liberty in meters",
"answer": 93
},
{
"question": "Weight of the largest recorded giant squid in kg",
"answer": 275
},
{
"question": "Number of keys on a standard piano",
"answer": 88
},
{
"question": "Length of the Blue Whale in meters (average max)",
"answer": 30
}
]
